亲爱的  你可以帮我把盘子拿下来吗
Hey,hon? Would you help me get the plates down?
好的  嘿  我有个主意
Yeah. Hey,here's an idea.
今天用我们的结婚瓷器好不好
Why don't we use our wedding china today?
不  我只是认为 我们应该把瓷器留到
No,I just think we should save our china
真正特别的场合使用
for something really special.
像是英国女王来访的时候
Like if the queen of England comes over.
亲爱的  她一直爽约
Honey,she keeps canceling on us.
你该懂那是什么意思
Take the hint.
打破了怎么办呢  它们可是很贵的
What if something breaks? They're expensive.
东西摆着不用  意义何在呢
What is the point of having them if we never use them?
好吧  但是如果打破了
Okay. But if something breaks
然后女王又要来访
and then the queen comes over..
我会跟她解释的
I will explain it to her.
你以为我会让你跟她说话啊
Like I'd let you talk to the queen.
哇  今年的游行真是棒
Wow,the parade is really good this year.
天啊  那些马还真能拉屎
Man,those horses can crap.
下一个游行队伍是来自
Next up is a marching band
奥克拉荷马州的马斯科吉
from Muskogee,Oklahoma.
马斯科吉  离塔尔萨才四小时车程
Muskogee? That's like four hours from Tulsa!
接下来是来自
And here's the float with
日间肥皂剧《我们的日子》的众星们
the stars of the popular daytime soap.. Days of Our Lives.
噢  我的天
Oh,my God!
你不也参演了热门日间肥皂剧
Aren't you one of the stars of the popular daytime soap
《我们的日子》吗
Days of our Lives?
对啊  我忘了  我应该要参加游行的
Yeah. I forgot! I'm supposed to be there!
我不敢相信我忘了
I can't believe I forgot!
我通常会写在手臂上的
I usually write stuff like this down on my arm!
该死的长袖衣服
Stupid long sleeves!
你要怎么办呢
What are you gonna do?
我得找个好借口说明
I'll come up with a good reason..
我为什么没有到场
why I wasn't there.
制作人一定会很生气
The producers are gonna be mad.
他们昨天把我们叫进去说
They sat us down and said:
"大家都要在早上六点整到
"Everyone has to be there,6 a.m. sharp.
尤其是你  崔比安尼"
That means you,Tribbiani."
好像我是什么笨蛋似的
Like I was some kind of idiot.
你刚证明了他们是错的
Well,you proved them wrong.
《老友记》  第九季 第8集  瑞秋的另一个妹妹
Friends S09E08 The One With Rachel's Other Sister
噢  艾玛
Oh,Emma.
这是你第一个感恩节
This is your first Thanksgiving.
你要感谢什么呢
What are you thankful for?
妈咪的乳房吗
Mommy's boobies?
很多人都会感谢那东西的
A lot of people are thankful for those.
嗨  瑞秋
Hello? Rachel?
是谁
Who is it?
是你最喜欢的妹妹
It's your favorite sister.
吉儿  艾米
Jill?  Amy!
把我的戒指藏起来
Hide my rings.
艾米  感恩节快乐
Amy! Happy Thanksgiving.
你有没有直发器呢
Do you have a hair straightener?
直发器
Hair straightener.
我好像一年没有见到你了
I haven't seen you in,like,a year.
我知道  我知道  我忙坏了
I know. I know. I've just been crazed.
噢  我也是  我生了小孩
Well,me too. I had a baby.
我把爸的办公室重新装璜了一次
I decorated Dad's office.
是吗  除非你把桌子从阴道挤出来
Yeah? Well,unless you pushed a desk out of your vagina,
否则那可不能相提并论
not the same thing.
听着  关于直发器的事
Listen, about that hair straightener,
亲爱的  我真的需要
honey,I really need one.
我要到我男朋友家用晚餐
I'm gonna have dinner at my boyfriend's house.
噢  我的天
Oh,my God.
那是艾美特吗
Is this Emmett?
是艾玛
It's Emma.
是个女孩
It's a girl?
嗨  艾米
Hey,Amy.
艾米  你记得罗斯吧
Amy,you remember Ross?
不太记得
Not really.
但是你比她之前的呆头鹅男友可爱多了
But you are much cuter than that geeky guy she used to date.
那人就是我
That was me.
不  他是高中时代的怪男生
No,he was this creepy guy from high school
好像从九年级开始就很喜欢她的
who had this huge crush on her since,like,the ninth grade.
那还是我
Still me.
不  我不是在说你
No,I'm not talking about you.
就是你那个胖朋友的哥哥
It was your fat friend's brother
留着可笑的黑人头
with that bad Afro.
好了  艾米  我来给你节省点时间吧
Okay,Amy,I'm gonna save you some time,okay?
都是我
All me!
小心  小心
Careful. Careful.
小心
Careful!
不如这样吧  下半辈子
I'll tell you what. For the rest of our lives..
我都会很小心  除非你另有指示
I'll be careful until told otherwise.
这不是我们选的瓷器  我知道
This isn't the china we picked out.  I know.
你离开店里之后  我选了别的
After you left the store,I chose different ones.
为什么  无意冒犯  亲爱的
Why?  No offense, honey.
你的品味对我而言太女性化了
Your taste is a little feminine for me.
花朵图案就显得女性化吗
Suddenly flowers are feminine?
嘿  大家好  感恩节快乐
Hey,everybody! Happy Thanksgiving!
感恩节快乐  菲比
Happy Thanksgiving. Phoebe!
怎么了  乔伊
What's going on,Joe?
听着  我需要编个天衣无缝的谎
Listen,I need a good lie.
好的
Okay.
"阿波罗登月"那个谎言如何
How about the whole "man walking on the moon" thing,you know?
根本就可以看到线  愚民们
You can see the strings,people!
不  不  我需要一个谎言来解释
No,no,no. I need a good lie to explain
为什么我今天错过了一件工作上的事
why I wasn't at a work thing today.
亲爱的  你说谎技术烂透了
Honey,you stink at lying.
才不是呢
I do not.
是吗  让我问你
Really? Let me ask you something.
昨天发生在咖啡屋的事
Yesterday at the coffeehouse..
我去上厕所
I went to the bathroom.
回来的时候  我的松饼就不见了
When I came back,my muffin was gone.
是谁拿走的
Who took it?
有人打开咖啡屋的大门
Somebody opened the door to the coffeehouse..
然后一只浣熊就跑进来
and a raccoon ran in
直接拿走你的松饼  我说
and went straight for your muffin. I said:
"嘿  不能吃  那是菲比的"
"Hey,don't eat that! That's Phoebe's!"
然后他说
And he said..
他说"乔伊  你说谎技术烂透了"
He said,"Joey,you stink at lying."
我该怎么办呢
What am I gonna do?
别担心  我们会想个好谎言的
Don't worry. We'll come up with a lie.
我会帮你练习的
I'll help you practice.
太好了  太棒了  谢谢你
Great. That'd be great. Thank you.
没问题  你错过了什么工作的事
Sure. What was the work thing?
"到机场接奶奶"  噢  天啊
"Pick up Grandma at the airport."  Oh,man!
她真是我的心肝宝贝
She's precious.
你会不会担心
Do you ever worry
她会遗传到你整容前的鼻子
that she's gonna get your real nose?
艾米
Amy..
是的  我会  我真的担心
Yes,I do. I really do.
喂
Hello?
是  等一下 我可以到楼上讲吗
Yeah,hang on,one sec. Can I take this upstairs?
当然  我们不住在楼上  但是
Sure. We don't live there,but..
不是吧  只有这几间房间
Seriously? It's just these rooms?
我以为你是有钱的医生（博士）呢
I thought you were a doctor.
不  罗斯有博士学位
Yeah. No,Ross has a Ph.D.
天啊  她简直不可理喻
God,she is unbelievable.
对啊  博士学位就跟医学学位一样好啊
I know. I mean,a Ph.D. is just as good as an MD.
是噢  罗斯  对啊
Sure,Ross,yeah!
如果我在餐厅心脏病发
If I have a heart attack at a restaurant,
我会希望你带着化石刷站在一边
I want you there with your fossil brush.
该死的感恩节  怎么了
Stupid Thanksgiving.  What?
怎么了  发生什么事
What? What happened?
我男朋友取消跟我的约会了
My boyfriend canceled on me.
我好不容易才找到一段真感情
I mean,I finally find a real relationship.
一个可以跟我共度今天的人
Someone that I can spend this day with,
然后他老婆竟然回来了
and then his wife comes back into town!
我发誓  跟已婚男人约会真是不值得
I swear,it's almost not even worth dating married guys.
别这样说
Don't say that.
天啊  我本来很期待今天的
God,I was so looking forward to this.
本来会是很美好的感恩节的
It was gonna be such a beautiful Thanksgiving.
我们本来要吃寿司的
We were gonna have sushi.
艾米  别哭
Amy,don't cry.
罗斯  我可以私下跟你谈谈吗
Ross,can I talk to you in private?
当然  你想要去楼上或是
Sure,you wanna go upstairs,or..?
听着  我在想  如果莫妮卡不介意的话
Look,I was thinking,if it's okay with Monica..
我想邀请艾米跟我们共度感恩节
I would like to invite Amy to Thanksgiving.
我认为这是个好主意
You know, I think that's a great idea.
就像清教徒
It'll be like the Pilgrims
把梅毒带给美国印地安人一样
bringing the Indians syphilis.
听着  我知道她有点难搞
Look,I know she's a little tough to take.
但是  她没有其他地方可以去了
But she has nowhere else to go,
而且她是我妹妹  是艾玛的阿姨
and she's my sister. She's Emma's aunt.
我希望她们相处融洽
And I would like them to bond.
好吧  但我不想她们相处太融洽
Ok, fine. I don't want them bonding too much.
我不要她告诉艾玛说  她需要鼻部整形
I don't want her telling Emma she needs a nose job.
罗斯  她很可能会需要的
Ross,she may need one.
我们也只能接受了
We're just gonna have to make our peace with that!
嘿  大伙儿  这是我妹妹艾米
Hey,you guys. This is my sister,Amy.
这是钱德  乔伊  菲比
This is Chandler,Joey,Phoebe,
还有你认识的莫妮卡
and you know Mon.
噢  我的天
Oh,my God.
你有演《我们的日子》
You're on Days of Our Lives!
是的
Yeah.
哇  他们一定是帮你化很浓的妆
Wow! They must put a lot of makeup on you.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
欢迎  这是你第一次见到艾玛吗
So welcome. Is this the first time you're seeing Emma?
是的  我想是的
Yeah,I think so.
很高兴认识你  艾玛
It's nice to meet you,Emma.
菲比  声音真好玩
Phoebe.  That's a funny noise.
菲比  我还需要你帮忙  好的
Phoebe? I still need some help here.  Right. Okay.
不止是你说的谎言本身
So it's not just the lie you tell,
你说的方式也很重要  例如
but it's the way you tell it. For example..
如果你说谎的时候看着地上
if you look at the ground when you're talking,
人们就知道你在说谎
people know you're lying.
我不知道为什么说谎对我如此困难
I don't know why this is so hard for me.
说谎基本上就跟演戏一样
Lying is basically just acting..
而我可是演技精湛的演员
and I am a terrific actor.
你是演技"精湛"的演员
You are a terrific actor.
嘿  宝宝在哪呢
Hey. Where's the baby?
我们刚把她抱去睡了
We just put her down for a nap.
听着  我刚刚在想
Listen,I was just thinking.
你们知道什么会很棒吗
You know what would be incredible?
就是如果你们死了
If you guys died!
谢谢你  艾米
Thank you,Amy.
不  然后我就可以得到宝宝
No,no,then I would get the baby.
就像是电影情节一样
It would be just like a movie.
刚开始我会全无头绪
At first I wouldn't know what to do with her.
然后时机来临时
And then I would rise to the occasion.
我会完全改变  然后结婚
Then I'd get a makeover and get married.
真棒的电影
That's a great movie!
听着  反正你们也不能阻止我
Now,listen,not that you guys could stop me or anything..
因为你们已经死了
because you know,you'd be dead.
但是我想要帮她改名字
But I was thinking about changing her name.
我就是不大喜欢艾米丽
I'm just not really a big fan of Emily.
艾玛
Emma.
艾玛  罗斯在叫你
Emma? Ross wants you.
菲比
Phoebe!
她为什么一直发出那种怪声呢
Why does she keep making that noise?
亲爱的  我不知道要如何告诉你
Honey,I don't know how to tell you this..
但如果我跟罗斯发生了什么事
but if something were to happen to Ross or myself..
你不会得到宝宝的
you wouldn't get the baby.
那  谁会呢
Well,who would?
我们还没有正式问过他们
Well,we haven't officially asked them yet..
但我们希望是莫妮卡跟钱德
but we would want Monica and Chandler.
我不敢相信你们要我们抚养艾玛
I can't believe you'd want us to raise Emma.
噢  我的天  我真是太感动了
Oh,my God,I'm so moved.
我不敢相信  等一下  你们死了
I don't believe this. Hold on a second. You guys die..
然后宝宝不是我的
and I don't get your baby?
艾米  我们跟莫妮卡跟钱德比较亲近
Amy,see,we're a lot closer to Monica and Chandler.
我们每天都见面
We see them every day.
而且老实说  你好像也不太亲近宝宝
And truthfully,you don't seem connected to the baby.
亲近  亲近什么  她只是一堆肉
Connected? To what? She's a lump.
我必须跟你们说  这对我意义重大
You know,guys,I've gotta say this means so much to me.
我是说  你们肯相信我
I mean,that you would trust me
把孩子托付给我
with your child.
大家都知道莫妮卡跟我一直试着
I mean,we all know that Monica and I have been..
想要生小孩
trying to have a baby of our own.
我也有怀疑过  自己当父亲的能力
You know,I've had my doubts about my skills as a father,
但是  你们两个
but.. that you two..
你们两个  这个人吗
That you two..  This guy?
真的吗
Seriously?
好了  晚餐时间到了
Okay,it's time for dinner.
各位  我们将使用我们的高档瓷器
Everyone,we're using our fancy china..
它们是很贵的  所以请小心
and it's very expensive,so please be careful.
好了  再说明一次
Okay,just to be clear,
不要拿这些盘子开玩笑
comedy with the plates will not be wellreceived.
为什么我的盘子不如别人的高档
How come my plate's less fancy than everyone else's?
你不信任我  不让我用你的高档餐盘吗
Do you not trust me with a fancy plate?
不  亲爱的  那是特别的盘子
No,honey. That's a special plate.
其实是一个游戏
See,it's a game.
拿到那盘子的人就是赢家
Whoever gets that plate wins.
我不敢相信我赢了
I can't believe I won!
简直就像狠狠扇了我一耳光
You know,this is such a slap in the face.
我是说  我是你妹妹
I mean,I'm your sister..
你却把宝宝给这些陌生人  而不给我
and you would give your baby to these strangers over me.
莫妮卡是罗斯的妹妹
Monica is Ross' sister.
不  罗斯的妹妹很肥的
No,Ross' sister was really fat.
那就是我
That was me.
不  她上学时是个蠢蠢的女生
No,she was this dorky girl in school
就像小狗一样跟着瑞秋
who followed Rachel around like a puppy..
艾米  你不能再这样了
Amy,you've got to stop doing that!
好了  我知道你现在正在经历家庭危机
Okay,listen,I know you're having a bit of a family crisis..
但你不需要把气出在盘子身上
but you don't have to take it out on the plates.
其实我认为每个人
I mean,in fact,I think that everyone..
都应该这样切食物
should cut their food like this:
瞧见了吗
Now,see?
像这样  不只可以保护盘子
This way,you protect the plates..
而且老实说  还挺好玩的
and let's face it,you have fun.
好吧  那这样呢  如果你们死了
Okay,how about this? If you guys die..
而且疯狂盘子女士也死了
and the crazy plate lady dies..
那我可以得到宝宝吗
then do I get the baby?
不  如果疯狂盘子女
No,if crazy plate lady..
如果莫妮卡死了
If Monica dies,
那艾玛就是我的了  对吗
then I would get Emma. Right?
其实  其实怎样
Well,actually..  Actually what?
只是  如果是那样的话
It's just.. It's just that in that case..
那艾玛就去跟我父母一起生活
then Emma would go to my parents.
什么  很伤心  对不对
What?  Hurts,doesn't it?
我要等谁死了才能得到她
Who has to die for me to get her?
所以如果莫妮卡不在了
So if Monica's not around,
我就没有资格抚养艾玛了
I'm not good enough to raise Emma?
不  我们不是这个意思
No,that is not what we're saying.
他在说谎  他看了地上
Yeah,he's lying. He looked down.
我有什么不好的呢  我无法胜任吗
Well,what's wrong with me? Am I incompetent?
最后活下来的可是我
Because I managed to survive
弄死你们三个的事故  没有弄死我
whatever it is that killed the three of you!
你可能有点误会
You're taking this the wrong way.
我们认为你会是很好的父亲
We think you are going to be a wonderful parent.
只是你是比较风趣的父亲
It's just.. You're more the,you know,fun parent.
是的  我们希望艾玛
Yeah,and we wanna make sure that Emma
也有像莫妮卡这样的人照顾
also has someone like Monica..
比较有纪律的人
who's more of a disciplinarian.
比较坚定  严格的人
Someone who can be firm and strict.
你们对我的感觉不是真的那样吧
That's not how you see me,is it?
不  你真的很有趣
No,you're all about the fun.
我或许不是很了解宝宝
I may not know a lot about babies,
但是你们真的认为我没有能力吗
but do you really think I'm not capable?
不  你们两个能力相当
No. You both are equally capable.
只不过你们在一起的时候是最强的
It's just you're strongest when you're together.
好的  如果我们一起得到艾玛
Okay. So if we both had Emma,
然后我死了
and I died..
她也不能拥有她
she'd have to give her up.
当然  莫妮卡也必须把她让出来
Sure. Monica would have to give her up.
我说谎说的至少比他好  对吧
I lie better than that,right?
让我说清楚
Let me just get this straight.
如果我的两个朋友死了  我得到艾玛
So my two friends die,I get Emma.
然后我老婆死了  那艾玛
Then my wife dies. Then Emma,
我生命中剩下的唯一一小块希望
the one tiny ray of hope left in my life..
也会从我身边被带走
gets taken away from me?
真是精彩的好电影
There's your movie.
嘿  你在这里
Hey,there you are.
你晚餐之后就消失了
You disappeared after dinner.
有人想念我吗
Did somebody miss me?
有婴儿需要被无能的父亲抚养长大吗
Was there a child to raise poorly?
罗斯跟瑞秋根本不知道在瞎说什么
Ross and Rachel don't know what they're saying.
他们自己也不是多有责任感
It's not like they're so responsible.
艾玛只不过是一瓶红酒
Emma is a product of a bottle of merlot
跟一个过期保险套的意外产物
and a fiveyearold condom.
不  他们是对的
No,but they're right.
我不是个坚强的父亲  我永远都不会是
I'm not a strong father figure,and I never will be.
不  这些是要学习的
No,you learn these things.
你会逐渐学会的
You grow into it.
是的  但那就不是我了
Yeah,but it's not who I am.
他们说的一切
Everything they said
都是我担心有小孩之后  会面对的问题
is exactly why I was worried about having a kid.
是真的
And it's true.
而且  大家都知道
And look,everybody knows it.
我不知道
I don't know it.
我要跟你生小孩因为
I wanna have a kid with you because
我认为你会是很棒的父亲
I think you'll be an amazing dad.
不管是风趣还是有纪律
At the fun parts and at the hard parts.
那你可以想像我说
Well,can you picture me saying,
"回房去  你被禁足了"吗
"Go to your room,you're grounded"?
你可以想像我说"你被禁足了"吗
Can you hear me say,"You're grounded"?
你上星期才那样对我说过
You said that to me last week.
是有多难做到
How hard is it?
我叫你不要穿着鞋子踏在家具上
"No shoes on the furniture!"
制作人刚刚留言
The producer from Days left a message
问我为什么没有参加游行
asking why I wasn't at the parade.
他说大家都对我很不爽
They said everybody's really pissed off at me.
而且他们都有见到圣诞老人
And they all got to meet Santa!
没关系  我帮你想了一个完美谎言
It's okay. I thought of the perfect lie for you.
很简单  很容易记
It's simple. It's easy to remember,
而且不会引来更多的问题
and it doesn't invite a lot of questions.
你没有参加游行
You weren't at the parade
是因为家里出了紧急状况
because you had a family emergency.
我喜欢耶  耶
I like that! Yeah!
我没有参加游行
I wasn't at the parade
是因为家里出了紧急状况
because I had a family emergency.
发生什么事
What happened?
我妹的浣熊  不  别提浣熊
My sister's raccoon came..  No,nothing with a raccoon!
等等  你们在做什么 摆餐具
Wait,what are you doing?  Setting the table.
我们觉得用这些高档餐盘
We thought it might be nice to use the fancy china
来吃甜点也很不错
for dessert too.
很不错  或许等一下我们可以
How nice. Maybe later we can
去拿我的结婚礼服来擤鼻涕
all go blow our noses on my wedding dress.
嘿  兄弟  你还好吗
Hey,dude,you okay?
刚刚的事我很抱歉
Sorry about before.
没关系  你完全是对的
That's okay. You're totally right.
我根本就不知道如何管教孩子
I don't know anything about disciplining a child.
但我还是很伤心
But it did hurt my feelings,
而且我要你知道  如果我死了
and I want you to know that if I die..
你别想得到乔伊
you don't get Joey.
如果你还没注意到
In case you hadn't noticed,
我现在不会跟你说话的
I'm not talking to you.
真的是  是典型的瑞秋
You know,this is just.. This is classic Rachel.
对噢  记得在高中的时候
Oh,yeah,right. Remember in high school
我死了  也没有把婴儿给你吗
when I died and didn't give you my baby?
这或许是我唯一拥有小孩的机会  瑞秋
This might be my one chance to have a child,Rachel.
你知道我一直忙于我的事业
I mean,you know that I have been so busy focusing on my career..
什么事业  我是室内设计师
What career?  I'm a decorator.
你装璜了爸的办公室
You decorate Dad's office
就是设计师了吗
and now you're a decorator?
好吧  我昨天去了动物园
Okay,I went to the zoo yesterday,
现在我就是考拉熊了
now I'm a koala bear.
你为什么不能多支持我一点
Why can't you ever be supportive?
你要谈支持吗
You wanna talk supportive?
我在医院生小孩时
You didn't come and visit me
你可没有来看过我
when I was in the hospital having the baby!
我在医院做嘴唇整形时
You didn't come see me in the hospital
你也没有来看我
when I was getting my lips done!
我第一次有去
I did the first time.
说老实话   你想知道
You know what? You wanna know
我什么不把艾米丽给你吗
why I am not giving Emily to you?
是艾玛  你是站谁那边的
Emma.  Whose side are you on?!
我不给你艾玛
I'm not giving you Emma
是因为你无法扛起
because you can't handle
照顾小孩子的责任
the responsibility of a child.
那有多难  你都做得到
Well,how hard could it be? You do it.
你知道你为什么不想让我得到宝宝吗
You wanna know why you don't want me to have the baby?
因为你不想看到我快乐
Because you don't want me to be happy.
你总是在忌妒我
You have always been jealous of me.
忌妒你什么
Jealous of what?
忌妒你没有责任感吗  还是你的不成熟
Of your lack of responsibility? Your immaturity?
你那种完全忽略别人感受的作为吗
Your total disregard for other people's feelings?
那只是其中几项
To name a few.
其实  你总是这样
You know, you've always been like this.
你总是要所有的东西
You had to have everything,
而我什么都得不到
and I couldn't have anything.
就像在初中的时候  你抢走我的迪米
Like in junior high,when you stole Timmy from me.
你知道那伤我有多深吗
I mean,do you even realize how much that hurt me?
迪米当时是我的男朋友
Timmy was my boyfriend,
而你跟他偷偷亲热
and you made out with him!
别这样  那已经是20年前的事了
Come on,that was 20 years ago.
别老记着
Get over it.
我不敢相信我今天邀请了你
I cannot believe that I invited you here today!
是噢  你知道我不敢相信什么吗
Yeah,well,you know what I cannot believe?
我所谓的姐姐
That my socalled sister..
有罗夫罗兰七折的折扣优惠
gets a 30 percent discount from Ralph Lauren,
而我却要付零售价
and I still have to pay retail?
是五五折
It's 45.
你个贱人
You bitch.
你就是认为你很完美
You just think you're so perfect..
拥有你的新生儿  还有你的小公寓
with your new baby and your small apartment.
让我告诉你一件事
Well,let me tell you something.
你的宝宝并不怎么可爱
Your baby isn't even that cute.
太过分了  艾米  太过分了
Too far,Amy. Too far.
你收回那句话  不
You take that back.  No.
收回那句话
Take it back!
不  你能怎样呢  强迫我吗
No. What are you gonna do? Make me?
嘿  我有上健身房
Hey,man,I work out!
我也有  我有做普拉提
So do I.  I do Pilates.
我有做瑜伽  放马过来
I do yoga.  Bring it on!
盘子放到箱子里  盘子放到箱子里
Put the plates in the boxes! Put the plates in the boxes!
你刚刚推了我吗  是的  没错
Did you just push me?  Yeah,I think I did.
好了  够了
All right,that's it.
别管泡泡包装了  没有时间了
Forget the bubble wrap! There isn't time!
卷发  卷发  卷发
Frizzy,frizzy,frizzy!
天啊  我们应该阻止她们吗
Oh my god, Shouldn't we stop this?
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
我们应该倒一些果冻到她们身上
Let's throw some JellO on them!
恶心
Gross!
好了  到此为止
All right,that is it!
这是我们家 你们不可以有这种行为
This is our apartment,and you cannot behave this way!
如果你们不能表现得像成人
If you can't act your age,
你们就不应该在这里
you shouldn't be here at all.
那些瓷器或许没有
Those plates may not be
我挑的那些粉红色瓷器好看
as nice as the pretty pink ones that I picked out..
但是它们对莫妮卡很重要
but they're important to Monica.
我要你们现在就向她道歉
And I want you to apologize to her,now.
我很抱歉  莫妮卡  我很抱歉
I'm sorry.  Mon,I'm so sorry.
好了  这样好多了
Okay. That's better.
现在  我要你们诚心地向彼此道歉
Now,I want you to apologize to each other and mean it.
对不起  对不起
Sorry.  Sorry.
对了  刚才那场架真是让人情欲高涨
By the way,that fight was totally arousing.
老兄  干的好
Dude,well done.
如果我跟瑞秋还有莫妮卡死了
If I die and Rachel dies and Monica dies,
你可以照顾艾玛
you can totally take care of Emma.
是吗  谢谢
Yeah? Well,thanks.
那  那我可以得到乔伊吗
So.. So now do I get Joey?
好的  但是你得知道他一天吃五餐
Okay. But you should know he eats a lot
而且还会塞硬币到鼻孔里
and shoves pennies up his nose.
你还好吗  莫妮
Are you okay,Mon?
这种事常发生的
I mean,these things happen.
只不过是盘子而已
I mean,it's just a plate.
又不是有人死了
It's not like somebody died.
没关系的  你可以哀悼的
It's all right. You can mourn.
谢谢你  这些本来都很漂亮的
Thank you. It was so beautiful!
我要去乔伊家拿几个派
I'm gonna go to Joey's and get the pies.
事实上  不是几个派  只剩一个派了
Actually,not pies. It's just pie.
我不在乎
I don't care.
天啊  我已经失去骂人的力气了
Oh,my God,I've lost the will to scold.
听着  艾米
Look,Amy..
我们有一点
we got a little..
刚刚有一点失控
a little outofcontrol over there.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
你是我妹妹
You're my sister..
如果你真的很在乎
and if it really means that much to you..
你要把宝宝给我了吗
So you're gonna give me the baby?
不  我只是
No,I was..
我只是想让你用我的罗夫罗兰折扣卡
I was gonna let you use my Ralph Lauren discount.
你不会后悔的
You are not gonna regret this.
她要换尿布了
She needs changing.
不  不  不  让我去
No,no,no. I'll get her.
我超级有自信  完全有责任感
I am super confident,totally responsible
而且是第4位有资格抚养艾玛的人
and fourth in line to raise Emma.
我马上就来  艾玛
I'll be right there,Emma!
先让我拿一下我的尿片袋子
Just let me get my trusty diaper bag here.
老实说  我觉得我将是第一个死的人
Well,what do you know? I guess I'll be the one who dies first.
莫妮卡知道你打碎她瓷器的事吗
Does Monica know about you breaking her plates yet?
不知道
Nope.
全都打破了  是吗  是的
Broke them all,huh?  Yep.
你要告诉她吗 不想
You gonna tell her?  Nope.
嘿  我要把这些盘子放回去
Hey. So I'm gonna put the plates back.
我想你是对的
I think you're right.
我们近期内不应该再用这些盘子了
We shouldn't use these plates for a long time.
只有女王来的时候才用吗
Like only if the queen comes?
或许那时候也不该用
Maybe not even then.
嘿  我办到了
Hey. I did it.
我告诉我的制作人说
I told my producer
我家里发生紧急事件
I had a family emergency.
他完全相信我
He totally bought it.
谢谢你教我如何说谎  菲比
Thanks for teaching me how to lie, Phebs
不用客气  下星期教你偷窃
No problem. Next week,stealing.
再见  盘子
Bye,plates.
你告诉她你打破所有的盘子了
You told her you broke all the plates?
什么  盘子发生什么事了吗
What?! Something happened with the plates?
是啊  一只浣熊跑进来
Yeah,this raccoon came in..